<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-04-28T09:17:07-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hey, I’m Stephen – Here’s What I Build</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hey, I’m Stephen – Here’s What I Build" /><published>2025-04-24T05:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-04-24T05:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/04/24/welcome-to-jekyll.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi there 👋 — I’m <strong>Stephen Hukish</strong>, a senior front-end engineer with full-stack chops and a passion for building high-impact tools, elegant interfaces, and now, intelligent systems powered by AI.</p>

<p>Over the last 15+ years, I’ve worked with companies ranging from small dev studios to major players like <strong>Shopify</strong> and <strong>Scotiabank</strong>, shipping scalable products across commerce, banking, and internal platforms.</p>

<h3 id="what-i-build">What I Build</h3>

<ul>
  <li>✨ <strong>Interfaces that scale</strong>: From internal dashboards to global storefronts, I craft fast, accessible front-ends using React, TypeScript, and modern frameworks.</li>
  <li>🧠 <strong>AI-infused features</strong>: At Shopify, I worked on <strong>Sidekick</strong>, integrating LLMs (OpenAI/Anthropic) into merchant tools for smarter commerce.</li>
  <li>🧰 <strong>Full-stack solutions</strong>: I’ve built APIs and backend tools in Ruby on Rails and Node.js, with a focus on developer experience and maintainability.</li>
  <li>🚀 <strong>Platform upgrades</strong>: I love solving big foundational problems — things like Webpack migrations, Apollo upgrades, DX tooling, and CI pipelines.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="why-this-blog-exists">Why This Blog Exists</h3>

<p>I’m using this space to:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Share side projects and experimental tools.</li>
  <li>Write dev notes on AI integrations, front-end performance, or cool tech.</li>
  <li>Reflect on lessons from big projects and transitions (like being let go from Shopify — yep, it happens).</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="lets-connect">Let’s Connect</h3>

<p>If you’re building something ambitious (especially in the AI, devtools, or UX space) — I’d love to hear from you.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>You can find my full resume <a href="http://dahukish.github.io">here</a>, or shoot me an email at <a href="mailto:stephen.hukish@gmail.com">stephen.hukish@gmail.com</a>.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Cheers,<br />
<strong>Stephen</strong></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there 👋 — I’m Stephen Hukish, a senior front-end engineer with full-stack chops and a passion for building high-impact tools, elegant interfaces, and now, intelligent systems powered by AI.]]></summary></entry></feed>